<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on DeFiGeek Community</title><link>/en/</link><description>Recent content in Home on DeFiGeek Community</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-JP</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>July-Sept 2022 financial report</title><link>/en/blog/july-sept-2022-financial-report/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/july-sept-2022-financial-report/</guid><description>Key highlights ・Due to recent (Sept 2022) change in personnel in charge of Finance Department, there are disconnects of data, accounting treatment and accounting assumption between this report and report published in previous months. No retrospective application has been applied due to limitation of available data.
・Gross Burn Rate: Total cash outflow (expense items: interest expense, relayers fee, labor cost, gas cost, incentives, etc.)
・Net Burn Rate: Total Cash Flow (Gross Burn Rate + Rewards Claimed, interest earned and Airdrop received)</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Banner</title><link>/en/brand_assets_banner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/brand_assets_banner/</guid><description>You can get images directory after read the note at BrandAsset.</description></item><item><title>Brand Asset</title><link>/en/brand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/brand/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Join</title><link>/en/join/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/join/</guid><description>The DeFiGeek Community is looking for contributors in various fields.
Developer team Smart contract (Solidity) Web3 front end E2E test with like Cypress Web page on on-chain DAO Design team Web design Illustrator Making infographic PR team Making web site Writing guide book and articles Translate Finance team Review monthly finance report Treasury management We define &amp;ldquo;Tasks&amp;rdquo; as items we need to improve for growing our community.</description></item><item><title>TXJP</title><link>/en/txjp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/txjp/</guid><description>TXJP Token Total Supply: 210,000TXJP Decimals: 8 TXJP contract address: 0x961dd84059505d59f82ce4fb87d3c09bec65301d TXJP is the DeFiGeek Community native token. DeFiGeek Community runs own treasury fund. We consider treasury strategies and TXJP holders can vote to adopt or reject its strategies using TXJP. The TXJP fund is a seed investor that invests in new Dapp and tools developed by DFGC. Benefit of TXJP holder A portion of the new Dapp tokens developed by the community will be allocated to TXJP holders.</description></item></channel></rss>