<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on DeFiGeek Community</title><link>/en/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on DeFiGeek Community</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-JP</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Development Updates September 2022</title><link>/en/blog/development-updates-september-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/development-updates-september-2022/</guid><description>Introduction DFGC has been developing several DeFi &amp;amp; NFT projects. They are ongoing in an undisclosed manner in order to protect our ideas &amp;amp; codes from being stolen.
The purpose of publishing this report is to secure transparency of our development activity to some extent &amp;amp; increase public awareness of our activity to attract people to join &amp;amp; be contributors to our community.
Progress Report YAMATO Core Development The first audit report has been finalized.</description></item><item><title>July-Sept 2022 financial report</title><link>/en/blog/july-sept-2022-financial-report/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/july-sept-2022-financial-report/</guid><description>Key highlights ・Due to recent (Sept 2022) change in personnel in charge of Finance Department, there are disconnects of data, accounting treatment and accounting assumption between this report and report published in previous months. No retrospective application has been applied due to limitation of available data.
・Gross Burn Rate: Total cash outflow (expense items: interest expense, relayers fee, labor cost, gas cost, incentives, etc.)
・Net Burn Rate: Total Cash Flow (Gross Burn Rate + Rewards Claimed, interest earned and Airdrop received)</description></item><item><title>Yamato Protocol V1 Overview</title><link>/en/blog/yamato-protocol-v1-overview/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/yamato-protocol-v1-overview/</guid><description>Summary Yamato Protocol is a crypto-asset overcollateralized stable coin issuance protocol.
V1 allows the issuance of CJPY (&amp;ldquo;Convertible JPY&amp;rdquo;, a Japanese Yen equivalent coin) using ETH as collateral.
It has the following features
No immediate forced liquidation No obligation to repay debt No interest rates (Fee collected at the time of borrowing) Low secured rates (minimum 130%) Additional features, Governance token, vote-escrowed mechanism and Pledge for CUSD &amp;amp; CEUR are to come in V1.</description></item></channel></rss>